Retry bugs hide behind successful happy paths. RetryProof turns one into a controlled, repeatable flight test.
I start with a synthetic n8n refund workflow. RetryProof inspects only supported structure and synthetic data. It never executes uploads, contacts the network, or calls a real payment service.
The seeded judge path uses an honestly labeled cached GPT-5.6 contract. The custom-workflow path is separately live-verified with GPT-5.6 Sol. The model proposes; it cannot approve or judge.
A human approves one narrow invariant: for each event ID, create at most one refund effect across retries.
The simulator injects a timeout after the first mock refund commits. One event, two deliveries, two effects. The contract is red.
A fresh Codex SDK thread runs with high reasoning in a read-only, network-disabled sandbox and may return only the bounded patch shape.
The wait is compressed. Worker-side validators bind the source and trusted fixture, reject undeclared output, and replay the counterexample.
The identical seed, fault, and two deliveries now produce one effect. Before: two and fail. After: one and pass.
The receipt binds the source, approved invariant, scenario, traces, repair, validation results, and limitations.
GPT-5.6 proposes. A human approves. Codex repairs. Deterministic software proves. That is RetryProof.